RODRICK VYIZIGIRO

• DETAILS •

778-239-3874 rodrieInt@gmail.com

LINKS

My potfolio

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Typescript

Dart

Angular

jQuery

Git CI/CD

Agile methodology

Firebase

Flutter

Bloc Pattern

Clean Architecture

Domain Driven Design

Node.js

Bootstrap

GraphQL

Wire-framing & Prototyping (Figma)

• HOBBIES •

Hiking, cooking, public speaking, graphic design, cycling & reading.

PROFILE

I am a Junior web developer with 4 years of experience in website development and currently studying UX design. I have a well-rounded evident experience in front-end and back-end development. I am a pragmatic developer seeking a team to grow with.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Flutter Developer at Luminucx, Port coquitlam

June 2019 — May 2022

- Launched a successful multi-language web app in a flutter.
- Timely delivered a design & prototype of the app in Figma
- Created complex widgets for the use cases following clean architecture.
- Effectively conducted CI/CD using Git lab with my team
- Conducted performance testing & optimization on the app
- Worked on back-end authentication & database services.
- Documented & wrote part of a light framework that enforced clean architecture in the app.
- Collaborated & worked intensively with system designer on big decisions.

Web Developer Contract at Dr Mura Health, Remote

March 2020 — June 2021

- Created a course website with a CMS using angular for a remote client
- · Effectively collaborated with client to meet their needs
- Designed & prototype their website using AdobeXD
- Built a CMS that served their content management needs.
- Created storage, authentication and database services in Typescript
- Successful maintained the site serving users

Volunteered to create Remote Area Community Hotspots at TIES, Port Coquitlam

March 2022 — June 2022

Created RACHEL units with Raspberry-pi to serve students in third-world countries with access to educational websites & resources in an offline format.

EDUCATION

High School Deploma, Ebus Academy, Port Coquitlam

June 2023

COURSES

Google UX Design Certificate, Google

May 2022 — Present

2021 Flutter Development Bootcamp, udemy

■ REFERENCES

• References available upon request